## Lexi Allen

5991 S Pitkin CT, Aurora, CO, 80016, 662-549-4866, lexi.allen14@gmail.com

PROFILE	Healthcare Revenue Cycle professional with 5 years of experience in front and back end Revenue Cycle Management. Skilled in analyzing aging reports, utilizing deductive reasoning to problem solve, resolving complex outpatient billing claims, storytelling issues on accounts all while maintaining accuracy and details in my work.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Jun 2022 — Present	Cash Application Analyst , Ka	rcher	Aurora, CO
	<ul> <li>Responsible for managing financial transactions up to \$1M daily in lock-box and \$200k in credit cards</li> <li>Reconcile the sub ledger daily and accurately matches customer's remittance with invoices</li> <li>Research and post unidentified payments, and handle refunds</li> </ul>		
Mar 2021 — Jun 2022	Corporate Account Analyst, C Medicine	Colorado Center for Reproductive	Lone Tree, CO
	<ul> <li>Managed billing for 5 clinics with a monthly revenue of \$2M dollars</li> <li>Reported trends in processes at each clinic and assist with resolutions and implementation of new processes all while decreasing aging revenue by roughly \$100k-\$200k a month</li> <li>Presented detailed analysis of reimbursements to VP of Contracting and Revenue Cycle</li> <li>Audited billing and ensured services were authorized and coded accurately</li> </ul>		
Jul 2020 — Mar 2021	Business Administrative Assist	ant, Columbus Light and Water	Columbus, MS
	<ul> <li>Finalized billing and maintained records of delinquent accounts for customers</li> <li>Reconciled and prepared bank deposit for approximately \$100K in payments and provided teller services as needed</li> </ul>		
Sep 2017 — Jul 2020	Revenue Cycle Associate, Drag	ver Physical Therapy	Columbus, MS
	<ul> <li>Reconciled \$2M dollars of elect</li> <li>Completed EDI enrollments fo</li> <li>Appealed denials based upon re</li> </ul>	r commercial and government payers	
Aug 2016 — Jul 2017	Administrative Support Staff,	Children's Health Center	Columbus, MS
	<ul> <li>Conducted monthly time audits for providers and nurses, and handled daily patient data entry</li> <li>Assisted the front office with scheduling, insurance verification, and triage as needed</li> </ul>		
Oct 2015 — Aug 2016	Community Service Intern, M	ommunity Service Intern, Mississippi University for Women	
	<ul> <li>Coordinated and led 25 students in a home for Habitat for Humanity project</li> <li>Arranged facilities, program materials, advertising, transportation, food, and equipment for community service projects</li> </ul>		
EDUCATION			
Aug 2015 — May 2017	B.S in Healthcare Management, Mississippi University for Women		Columbus, MS
Aug 2013 — May 2015	A.S in Liberal Arts, East Mississippi Community College		Mayhew, MS
SKILLS AND SOFTWARE	Microsoft Excel	Raintree	
	Analytical Thinking	Centricity	
	Problem Solving	Waystar	
	A -1	CAD	

SAP

Google Workspace

Athena

Mac Practice